I would like to have your attention and viewers all over the world
for a special message of the Prophet for you and the whole world
which I'm going to read, in Jesus'name.
Our Prophet will not be able to be with us today but he is with us in the Spirit.
Special Message From Prophet T.B. Joshua
As you know and you have watched on Emmanuel TV,
he has been praying for you, praying for me and praying for the whole world.
You will remember the message he said that this year will be a very fearful year.
You can imagine the revelation he has.
He has to pray for God to give him wisdom on how to present this message to the world at large.
He has a message now for the nation Nigeria.
Message for Nigeria:
Nigeria should fast and pray this coming Thursday (17-01-19) and next upper Wednesday (23-01-19).
We should pray so that God should change the bad happenings he sees to good.
He is not permitted to say exactly what will happen.
So let us pray and fast Thursday and next upper Wednesday.
This revelation will be read to you the moment God gives him the wisdom to present it to you.
It will be given to you; it will be presented to you, in Jesus' name.
Say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
Let someone say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
Where God guides, He provides.
Where God guides, He protects.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
TT: Mel Flowers 19/01/2019